Contact

amazingnursesinc@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ashley-asberry (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Travel Nursing
Telemetry
Critical Care Nursing

Certifications
Real Estate Agent
CCRN

Ashley Asberry

An Amazing Nurse available to positively serve Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the health wellness and fitness industry. Skilled in Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Travel Nursing, Critical Care Nursing, Basic Life Support (BLS), and Telemetry. Strong professional with a Bachelor of Nursing focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from University of Oklahoma Health Sciences Center.

Experience

City Hospital at White Rock Registered Nurse January 2020 - Present (7 months) Dallas, Texas

BEMER Group USA
Independent BEMER Distributor
January 2019 - Present (1 year 7 months)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Health is wealth. Invest in yourself.

trustaff
Travel Registered Nurse
January 2011 - December 2019 (9 years)
United States

Accept assignments for 13 weeks duration in licensed states. Staffed in ICU, TELE and M/S TELE Willing to float to areas within my skill level

Baylor Scott & White Health PRN Nurse January 2019 - July 2019 (7 months) Sunnyvale, Texas Admissions, discharges and education. Float pool for ICU and cardiac stepdown.

Medical City Arlington
Registered Nurse
October 2018 - January 2019 (4 months)
3301 Matlock Rd, Arlington, TX 76015

Seasonal staff

Coast Medical Service Travel Registered Nurse June 2018 - August 2018 (3 months) Greater Los Angeles Area

Registry RN

Westways Staffing Services, Inc Travel Registered Nurse November 2017 - August 2018 (10 months) Los Angeles, California

Registry RN

Sutter Health Critical Care Registered Nurse April 2018 - May 2018 (2 months) Berkeley, CA

Care for intubated and sedated patient suffering COPD, CHF, CKD, ARF, DKA, Anemia, Sepsis, Pneumonia, GI bleed, ARDS, drug overdose, MI, SDH with evacuation and EVD placement or burr hole

Emerald Health Services
Travel Registered Nurse
December 2014 - March 2018 (3 years 4 months)
United States

13 weeks assignments with option to extend in my area of expertise ICU Floating to areas where competent

UCLA Health
Staff Registered Nurse
September 2015 - February 2018 (2 years 6 months)
Greater Los Angeles Area

Floats as a resource to all ICU, Med/Tele and surgical observation units (GOU, PTU, TRU, MPU, PACU boarding). Assist with continuing nurse education i.e. skills fair, new equipment, EMAR updates and simulation training.

Prive Care
Infusion Nurse
April 2017 - November 2017 (8 months)
Greater Los Angeles Area

Administer medications (hydration, TPN, IVIG, Factor Infusion) through IV access via PICC, Port or peripheral IV start.

Private duty for clients of privilege, in-home or in-hospital care with focus on Oncology patients primarily.

TCN Medical Staffing
Travel Registered Nurse
June 2010 - August 2017 (7 years 3 months)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Local jobs in the DFW area either contract or PRN

Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas) Staff Registered Nurse February 2010 - July 2011 (1 year 6 months) Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Initially hired as MS/TELE nurse with concentration in Endocrine support.

Completed an internship in the CVICU 3 months in duration from Nov 2010Feb 2011

Experience with LVAD, CVVHD and post op day 3 open heart patients.

Hillcrest Healthcare System
Staff Registered Nurse
August 2009 - February 2010 (7 months)
Tulsa, Oklahoma Area

Medical/surgical floor with primary focus on GI complications and treatments. Daily rounds with case management, pharmacy and unit manager to coordinate patient care during hospitalization and after discharge.

Education

University of Oklahoma Health Sciences Center
Bachelor of Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2007 - 2009)